MOSES KATONGO

ABOUT

I am a passionate individual with large interest in technology and innovation am an individual with at least an outstanding interpersonal, analytical and critical thinking skills. Poised to build valuable experience and ready to contribute to any team project or work with full commitment and effort according to my abilities.

Experience

2018-2019

Received award as the provincial best junior innovator.

 Simple chlorine production using batteries 2019–2020

Selected as Zambian ambassador to the United States of American for pan-African youth leadership Exchange program (PAYLP).

- Awarded honor of citizenship of Huntsville Alabama USA
- Won southern African pitch competition representing Zambia

2021-22

Founded TE&E Project Solutions Ltd company.

knowledge of:

web design, programming in C++, Data records and management, edible print production, technical writing, HTML and Java language.

Education

THE COPPERBELT UNIVERSITY, KITWE ZAMBIA

- Completed 1st year of study in the year 2021 COMPUTER ENGINEERING.
- Currently pursuing my 2nd year of study in COMPUTER ENGINEERING.

Communication

Fluent in English native language both written and speech and having great understanding of various tribal languages including (Nyanja, Tonga and bemba)

Skills and interest

-Computer specialist

- Microsoft Office

- Programming

-Gaming

- Exchange markets

- Guitarist

-Innovation and analysis

-Space

-Farming

References: Available upon request.



Contact

PO BOX 630655 CHOMA, ZAMBIA

: KITWE THE COPPERBELT UNIVERSITY, ROOM K1-136

.

+260973212775

mkatongo28@gmail.com

MOMOJR321 – GITHUB